# Luz Angela Gutierrez

**Greater Boston** 



linkedin.com/in/luz-angela-g-3256769b



lagguno@gmail.com

## Summary

Trained in Architecture, Urban Planning and Environmental Management, I am now transitioning to Web Development and UI/UX Design where I expect to utilize my previous training and experience to create a better user experience at all levels, responsive websites and great products.

# Experience



### **Computer Aided Design Drafter**

Kalwall Corporation

Mar 2020 - Present (3 months +)



## Architectural Designer

Landry Architects

Dec 2018 - Aug 2019 (9 months)



### Associate Designer

Art Form Architecture

Mar 2017 - Nov 2018 (1 year 9 months)



Lala's UP

Jan 2010 - Feb 2017 (7 years 2 months)



**Beitin Associates** 

2002 - 2007 (6 years)

# Project Architect

**Bolet Studio** 

2001 - 2001 (1 year)

### **Education**



### **III** University of New Hampshire

Certificate, Web Development

2020 - 2020



### 📕 Universidad Nacional de Colombia, Sede Medellin

**Environmental Management Diploma** 

1999 - 2000



## III Universidad Nacional de Colombia, Sede Medellin

Bachelor of Architecture (BArch), Validated by RIBA (Royal Institute of British Architects) 1989 - 1994

# Skills

Sustainability • Green Building • Architectural Design • Project Management • Project Planning • Site Planning • Job Scheduling • AutoCAD • Sustainable Design • SketchUp